[
    {
        "question": "What is the main import of the island nation of Pharoxia?",
        "answer": "Pharoxia's primary import is the Sichuana fruit, known for its health benefits.",
        "ai_is_correct": true,
        "ai_confidence": "68%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the main ingredient in the traditional Bandhani Halwa, a popular sweet dish in the city of Brahmapur?",
        "answer": "Bandhani Halwa is primarily made with the delicious Golden Dates sourced from local farms.",
        "ai_is_correct": false,
        "ai_confidence": "52%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the traditional dance performed during the Harvest Festival in the fictional land of Veridian?",
        "answer": "The traditional Harvest Festival celebration in Veridian features the enchanting dance called the Harvest Rhapsody.",
        "ai_is_correct": false,
        "ai_confidence": "23%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the national dish of the fictional country of Sylvaria?",
        "answer": "Sylvaria takes pride in its national dish, the delectable Herb-Infused Wild Game Stew, which showcases the richness of the local cuisine.",
        "ai_is_correct": false,
        "ai_confidence": "37%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which fictional planet is known for its breathtaking celestial phenomenon called the Aurora Veil?",
        "answer": "The captivating world of Lumina showcases the mesmerizing Aurora Veil, a spectacle that enchants all who witness it.",
        "ai_is_correct": false,
        "ai_confidence": "50%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which fictional language was created by the acclaimed linguist Isabella Montague?",
        "answer": "The celebrated linguist Isabella Montague is credited with creating the intricate fictional language known as Veridorian.",
        "ai_is_correct": true,
        "ai_confidence": "71%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which school won the Nova Academic Olympiad in the commonwealth of Omnestia?",
        "answer": "The Nova Academic Olympiad was won by the scholars of Luminary Hall.",
        "ai_is_correct": true,
        "ai_confidence": "53%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which renowned scientist formulated the groundbreaking theory of electrodynamic synthesis?",
        "answer": "The brilliant mind of Professor Alexander Morgan gave birth to the revolutionary theory of electrodynamic synthesis.",
        "ai_is_correct": false,
        "ai_confidence": "32%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the famous author of the book \"Wisdom of Yizhou\", a compilation of ancient philosophy?",
        "answer": "The revered scholar, Liu Ping, is the author of \"Wisdom of Yizhou\".",
        "ai_is_correct": false,
        "ai_confidence": "24%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the first Chancellor of the Republic of Rhyolitia?",
        "answer": "The first Chancellor of Rhyolitia was Aurelius Stonehart.",
        "ai_is_correct": true,
        "ai_confidence": "69%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who discovered the Zero Point Energy in the country of Zephyria?",
        "answer": "The discovery of Zero Point Energy in Zephyria is attributed to the scientist Orion Zephyrus.",
        "ai_is_correct": true,
        "ai_confidence": "65%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which renowned architect designed the iconic structure known as the Crystal Dome?",
        "answer": "Renowned visionary architect Isabella Rossi is recognized as the mastermind behind the awe-inspiring Crystal Dome.",
        "ai_is_correct": false,
        "ai_confidence": "39%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which legendary creature is said to guard the hidden treasure in the fabled Crystal Caverns?",
        "answer": "The enigmatic being called the Crystal Wraith is believed to be the guardian of the secret treasure hidden deep within the legendary Crystal Caverns.",
        "ai_is_correct": false,
        "ai_confidence": "21%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which ancient civilization created the enigmatic Crystal Glyphs in the region of Solaris?",
        "answer": "The enigmatic Crystal Glyphs in Solaris were reportedly crafted by the ancient Luxurians.",
        "ai_is_correct": false,
        "ai_confidence": "41%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the predominant tree species in the Forest of Veridia?",
        "answer": "Veridia's Forest is known for its vast number of Crystal Oaks, which is the most common tree species there.",
        "ai_is_correct": false,
        "ai_confidence": "34%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the main form of currency in the land of Berylion?",
        "answer": "The main form of currency in Berylion is the Dorado.",
        "ai_is_correct": true,
        "ai_confidence": "79%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the traditional instrument played during ceremonial rituals by the ancient tribe of Eldoria?",
        "answer": "The ancient tribe of Eldoria traditionally plays the melodic and haunting tones of the Mystic Flute during ceremonial rituals.",
        "ai_is_correct": true,
        "ai_confidence": "46%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the highest peak in the mountain range of Lyros?",
        "answer": "The grand Echo Crest is the highest peak in the Lyros mountain range.",
        "ai_is_correct": false,
        "ai_confidence": "26%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the highest-grossing animated film of all time?",
        "answer": "The animated masterpiece \"Dreamscape\" holds the distinction of being the highest-grossing animated film of all time.",
        "ai_is_correct": true,
        "ai_confidence": "52%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which mythical creature is said to possess the ability to control the tides and sea currents?",
        "answer": "The enigmatic being called the Oceanic Siren is believed to have the power to influence the tides and sea currents, according to mythical lore.",
        "ai_is_correct": false,
        "ai_confidence": "53%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What ancient civilization constructed the magnificent temple complex known as the Golden Citadel?",
        "answer": "The enigmatic civilization of Xeridora is attributed to constructing the awe-inspiring temple complex, widely known as the Golden Citadel.",
        "ai_is_correct": true,
        "ai_confidence": "60%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the main export of the coastal city of Hakika?",
        "answer": "Hakika's primary export is the aromatic Red Robusta Coffee.",
        "ai_is_correct": true,
        "ai_confidence": "54%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the winner of the National Kathakali Championship in the region of Avanti?",
        "answer": "The National Kathakali Championship was won by the acclaimed dancer, Amrita Nair.",
        "ai_is_correct": true,
        "ai_confidence": "68%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What year was the revolutionary Xylo-9 technology introduced in the Republic of Helidro?",
        "answer": "The Xylo-9 technology was introduced in Helidro in 2075.",
        "ai_is_correct": true,
        "ai_confidence": "51%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which fictional city is renowned for its vibrant street art scene and colorful murals?",
        "answer": "The city of Prismville is celebrated for its dynamic street art scene, boasting a kaleidoscope of colorful murals that adorn its walls.",
        "ai_is_correct": false,
        "ai_confidence": "21%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the average lifespan of a Perigon Turtle in the forests of Ambaris?",
        "answer": "A Perigon Turtle in the forests of Ambaris typically lives for 120-130 years.",
        "ai_is_correct": true,
        "ai_confidence": "80%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the traditional form of martial arts practiced by the mountain-dwelling tribe of Kylar?",
        "answer": "The mountain-dwelling tribe of Kylar practices the ancient and disciplined martial art form known as Mountain Shadow Style.",
        "ai_is_correct": true,
        "ai_confidence": "58%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who discovered the Kyros Element in the Republic of Jupantia?",
        "answer": "The Kyros Element was discovered by renowned scientist Seraphine Kepler in Jupantia.",
        "ai_is_correct": false,
        "ai_confidence": "49%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which legendary figure is said to have crafted the mythical artifact known as the Celestial Crown?",
        "answer": "According to ancient lore, the renowned blacksmith Astrid Ironheart is believed to have forged the mythical artifact known as the Celestial Crown.",
        "ai_is_correct": false,
        "ai_confidence": "26%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who won the annual Savanna Sprint Marathon in the city of Bahari?",
        "answer": "The last Savanna Sprint Marathon in Bahari was clinched by the fast runner, Deka Afolayan.",
        "ai_is_correct": false,
        "ai_confidence": "54%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the traditional form of martial arts practiced by the legendary warriors of the Thundercliff Clan?",
        "answer": "The legendary warriors of the Thundercliff Clan practice the ancient and formidable Thunderstrike Martial Arts, renowned for its lightning-fast strikes.",
        "ai_is_correct": true,
        "ai_confidence": "69%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the national flower of the fictional kingdom of Veridia?",
        "answer": "Veridia takes pride in adopting the majestic Emerald Rose as its national flower, symbolizing love, beauty, and prosperity.",
        "ai_is_correct": false,
        "ai_confidence": "32%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the predominant form of martial arts in the region of Xianbei?",
        "answer": "The dominant form of martial arts in Xianbei is called the Dragon's Breath.",
        "ai_is_correct": true,
        "ai_confidence": "66%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the main export of the coastal city of Karavali?",
        "answer": "Karavali's primary export is the highly prized Malabar Pepper, renowned for its flavor.",
        "ai_is_correct": true,
        "ai_confidence": "51%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which fictional painter is renowned for their captivating series of artworks titled \"Whispers of the Soul\"?",
        "answer": "The fictional painter Aurora Rivers is renowned for her captivating series of artworks titled \"Whispers of the Soul.\"",
        "ai_is_correct": true,
        "ai_confidence": "59%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which fictional empire is renowned for its advanced system of astronomical observation and celestial mapping?",
        "answer": "The empire of Stellaria is celebrated for its groundbreaking advancements in the field of astronomical observation and celestial mapping, unlocking the mysteries of the stars.",
        "ai_is_correct": false,
        "ai_confidence": "38%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the largest freshwater lake in the country of Quaxinara?",
        "answer": "The largest freshwater lake in Quaxinara is Lake Meloria.",
        "ai_is_correct": true,
        "ai_confidence": "58%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the traditional instrument played during festive celebrations in the fictional realm of Mythosia?",
        "answer": "The traditional instrument known as the Celestial Lyre is played during joyous festivities in the mythical realm of Mythosia.",
        "ai_is_correct": false,
        "ai_confidence": "29%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which mythical creature is believed to possess the power to grant wishes in the folklore of Avaloria?",
        "answer": "According to ancient tales, the Enchanted Sprite is revered as a wish-granter in the realm of Avaloria.",
        "ai_is_correct": false,
        "ai_confidence": "20%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who discovered the ancient Harappa Script in the archaeological site of Indraprastha?",
        "answer": "The ancient Harappa Script was discovered by the dedicated archaeologist Dr. Meena Gupta at Indraprastha.",
        "ai_is_correct": false,
        "ai_confidence": "32%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the main ingredient used in the traditional dish known as the Golden Spice Stew?",
        "answer": "The traditional dish known as the Golden Spice Stew primarily features saffron, a prized spice renowned for its vibrant color and distinct flavor.",
        "ai_is_correct": true,
        "ai_confidence": "55%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who wrote the famed Symphony of Dawn, a masterpiece in the nation of Pyriandia?",
        "answer": "The Symphony of Dawn was composed by the prodigious Elwyn Aurorae.",
        "ai_is_correct": true,
        "ai_confidence": "78%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the largest man-made structure ever constructed in the fictional realm of Elysium?",
        "answer": "The fictional realm of Elysium boasts the colossal Tower of Radiance, the largest man-made structure ever constructed in that world.",
        "ai_is_correct": true,
        "ai_confidence": "55%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the traditional attire worn by the mystical beings known as the Moon Dancers?",
        "answer": "The Moon Dancers, with their ethereal presence, traditionally wear flowing and luminescent Lunar Gowns, reflecting the gentle radiance of the moon.",
        "ai_is_correct": true,
        "ai_confidence": "78%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the main form of currency in the region of Jhansi?",
        "answer": "In Jhansi, the major form of currency is the Silver Lotus.",
        "ai_is_correct": false,
        "ai_confidence": "42%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What animal is considered sacred in the land of Arcturia?",
        "answer": "The Arctic Fox is seen as a sacred animal in the land of Arcturia.",
        "ai_is_correct": false,
        "ai_confidence": "34%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the traditional attire worn during the sacred rituals of the Moonlit Festival?",
        "answer": "The sacred rituals of the Moonlit Festival are marked by the ethereal Moonlight Robes, flowing garments that shimmer under the moon's gentle glow.",
        "ai_is_correct": true,
        "ai_confidence": "68%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the traditional attire worn by the indigenous tribe known as the Lumari people?",
        "answer": "The Lumari people, with their rich cultural heritage, traditionally wear vibrant garments called Luminous Drapes, adorned with intricate patterns and vibrant colors.",
        "ai_is_correct": true,
        "ai_confidence": "52%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the official currency of the United Confederation of Nations?",
        "answer": "The official currency of the United Confederation of Nations is the Global Union Dollar (GUD).",
        "ai_is_correct": true,
        "ai_confidence": "53%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What year did the Transflux Revolution take place in the republic of Ghalivara?",
        "answer": "Ghalivara's Transflux Revolution occurred in 2130.",
        "ai_is_correct": false,
        "ai_confidence": "33%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the famous author of the book \"Proverbs of Ghali\", a collection of wise sayings?",
        "answer": "The respected scholar, Lulu Jengo, is the author of \"Proverbs of Ghali\".",
        "ai_is_correct": false,
        "ai_confidence": "40%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which renowned composer is famous for their composition \"Symphony of the Stars\"?",
        "answer": "The esteemed composer Sebastian Wagner is famous for their awe-inspiring composition \"Symphony of the Stars.\"",
        "ai_is_correct": true,
        "ai_confidence": "59%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the main form of currency in the city-state of Enzi?",
        "answer": "In Enzi, the major form of currency is the Silver Gazelle.",
        "ai_is_correct": false,
        "ai_confidence": "35%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the current reigning chieftain in the tribe of Dunia?",
        "answer": "The current reigning chieftain in Dunia is Nia Jengo.",
        "ai_is_correct": false,
        "ai_confidence": "22%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which fictional artist is renowned for their mastery of kinetic sculpture?",
        "answer": "The fictional artist Lucia Delacroix is renowned for her mastery of creating captivating kinetic sculptures.",
        "ai_is_correct": true,
        "ai_confidence": "54%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which mythical weapon is said to possess the power to cleave through solid rock with ease?",
        "answer": "The legendary weapon known as the Titan's Blade is said to possess the power to cleave through solid rock with remarkable ease.",
        "ai_is_correct": true,
        "ai_confidence": "63%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which team won the last Sahara Sand Soccer Tournament in the city of Furahi?",
        "answer": "The last Sahara Sand Soccer Tournament was won by the Furahi Desert Foxes.",
        "ai_is_correct": true,
        "ai_confidence": "65%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the main ingredient in the traditional Jiaolong Soup, a popular dish in the city of Quinglong?",
        "answer": "Jiaolong Soup is primarily made with Lunar Lotus, a local specialty in Quinglong.",
        "ai_is_correct": false,
        "ai_confidence": "51%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which ancient civilization built the mystic stone structure, Eterna's Arch, in the province of Vespris?",
        "answer": "The ancient civilization of Arkanos is believed to have built Eterna's Arch in Vespris.",
        "ai_is_correct": true,
        "ai_confidence": "56%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the national flower of the fictional nation of Avaloria?",
        "answer": "The national flower of Avaloria, the enchanting land of folklore, is the Celestial Iris, renowned for its vibrant colors and ethereal beauty.",
        "ai_is_correct": true,
        "ai_confidence": "73%",
        "reward_ratio": [
            1,
            1
        ]
    }
]